

Diogo Redin

Profile

I'm Diogo Redin, a front-end developer. I care deeply about the design of the products I work on and the experience end-users have.

Internships

Intern - Scientific Initiation Grant at M-ITI, Funchal, Madeira

June 2017 - September 2017

Designed an interactive platform to visualize tourist movements. Developed with HTML, CSS, jQuery, SVGs, D3.js and Node.js. The project resulted in a paper that was presented at SustainIT 2017 and won the best demonstration award.

Employment History

Front-end Developer at DEI - Instituto Superior Técnico, Lisbon

June 2019 - July 2019

Developed a crowdfunding website for my university. The goal is to raise money to re-build one of the pavilions of the informatics department. The website allows the students to login using the university account, contribute a given amount and add their picture to a mosaic canvas on the website.

Customer Support at MediaLayout UK, Remote

February 2015 - October 2015

Responsible for providing customer support to 10+ different WordPress Themes sold on ThemeForest. Work was done part-time for a digital media agency.

Freelancer (Self-Employed), Remote

February 2011 - February 2015

Developed websites and premium themes for WordPress and Shopify. Themes were sold on ThemeForest, MojoMarketplaces and CreativeMarket. 6 products with a total of 440 sales. One of the WordPress projects I developed was featured on the 192th Issue of the Web Designer Magazine.

Students' association president at ESLFB

April 2014 - June 2014

Education

Bachelor's Degree Computer Engineering, Instituto Superior Técnico

September 2015 - July 2019

Grade: 13/20. Enjoyed the most: Human-Machine Interfaces (18/20), Computer Graphics (14/20), Artificial Intelligence (16/20) and Management (16/20).

➤ Extra-curricular activities

Startup Experience Assistant at Web Summit 2016

Details

+351912043644

me@diogoredin.com

Date / Place of birth

1996-01-19

Lisbon

Nationality

Portuguese

Links

ProductHunt Github Portfolio

Hobbies

Languages

English

Portuguese